Jesús Ferrer Galán

Software Developer

Contact

Address

Cullera, Valencia, 46400

Phone

+34 636 152 694

E-mail

jferrergalan@gmail.com







Skills

Laravel, React, React Native, Ionic, AngularJs.

PHP, JS, C# and Java

Version Control Systems: Git, Github

Web and Application Servers

Back-End and Database Skills

Agile Software Development

Responsive Web Design

Communication and Interpersonal Skills

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 6 months of related experience.

Work History

2021-06 Current

Full Stack Developer

Auto Recambios Vilber S.L, Valencia, Valencia

- Wrote server-side and client-side code for Business Management Systems projects using PHP, HTML, CSS, BootStrap, SQL, and JavaScript, specifically with the Laravel framework.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems, and corrected issues.
- Took initial concepts and developed project plans.
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.
- Adjusted design parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features.

2021-03 2021-05

Full Stack Developer

Ossian Technology, Paterna, Valencia

- Took initial concepts and developed project plans.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems, and corrected issues.
- Coordinated with other engineers to evaluate and improve software interfaces.
- Developed PrestaShop e-commerce website.
- CRM, ERP programming and layout using PHP, JS, SQL, CSS, HTML, BootStrap, and proprietary framework.

2015-01 2019-09

Children's Entertainer

Editorial SM, Valencia, Valencia

- Danced and conducted games encouraging children participation through playful antics and engagement.
- Adapted to various performance styles to suit diverse audiences.

Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS and BootStrap

Databases: SQL, MySQL and MariaDB

MVC Architecture

.NET Framework

Languages

English

Spanish

Valencian

Additional Information

Driving License

2015-07 2015-09

Supermarket Worker

Mercadona, Cullera, Valencia

- Rotated grocery products ensuring that expired or spoiled items were immediately removed and adhered to "first in, first out" rule.
- Checked for outdated and overripe grocery items and removed from inventory.
- Pleasantly greeted customers and provided prompt and courteous service at all times.

Education

2019-09 -

2021-06

Certificate of Higher Education:

Cross-platform Application Development

Florida University - Catarroja

 Professional development completed in Cross-platform Application Development.

2014-09 2019-06

Degree: History

University of Geography and History of Valencia. - Valencia

Certifications

2021-06	Best	Academic	Achievement	in	Certificate	of	Higher
	Education in Cross-platform Application Development						
2020-06	Preve	ention of risk	s at work				
2020-02	Media	ation and co	oflict resolution				